Only one chance to stop it
Asteroid-a-Geddon is a science fiction, action film directed by Geoff Meed.
A global scientific summit debates and fails on a plan to stop a massive asteroid heading
straight for Earth, with all countries blaming each other for the impeding disaster.
With communications tense, the daughter of a tech billionaire assembles her own team
of specialists to try to destroy the asteroid before it is too late.
General Quinn, played by Eric Roberts.
Alexandra, played by Veronika Issa.
Himari, played by Jennifer Lee Wiggins.
Malachi, played by Craig Gellis.
Chairman Pleasance, played by Terry Woodberry.
Roland, played by D'Artagnan Woods.
The Asylum is an American independent film company and distributor that
focuses on producing low-budget, direct-to-video films.
The company has produced titles that capitalize on productions by major studios, often using film titles
and scripts very similar to those of current blockbusters in order to lure customers.
These titles have been dubbed "mockbusters" by the press.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.